(Howard(to the real Raj who is daydreaming):)What ya thinking
so hard about?
(Raj:)Just that
I'm definitely not gay.
(Sheldon:)SHELDON
Penny!
Penny! Penny!
(Penny:)What's wrong?
(Sheldon:)Nothing.
I was acting.
(Penny:)You were acting.
(Sheldon:)Yes. In preparation
for today's studies,
I read Stanislavski's
An Actor Prepares,
Stella Adler's
The Technique of Acting,
Uta Hagen's
Respect for Acting,
and Henry Winkler's
Ayyy, I'm an Actor.
(Penny:)Well, good for you.
(Penny:)Come on in.
(Sheldon:)How shall we begin?
(Penny:)Well, I thought we'd start
(Sheldon:)with some
basic movement exercises.
(Penny:)You know, get our bodies
warmed up a little.
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Penny:)So I just want you to relax
(Penny:)and kind of
move around in the space.
(Penny:)You know,
just do whatever feels natural.